Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
- Krisher, Bernard - Love, Douglas O., and William D. Torrence., Publication (Box 15)
  - Lorenzo, Frank, "The Consumer and Deregulation", Publication (Box 15, Folder 138)
    - Item 1: Poland to Privatize Industry By Giving Stake to All Adults, 1991; Publication (Box 15, Folder 138)
      Author: Steve Lohr
  - "Loss of Manufacturing Jobs Due to Liquidations, Plant Closings and Other Major Layoffs", Publication (Box 15, Folder 139)
    - Item 1: Organizations Participation and Recession: An Analysis of Recent Evidence, 1987; Publication (Box 15, Folder 139)
      Author: Richard J. Long and Malcolm Warner
  - Lott, Jeffrey "Labor's Pains", Publication (Box 15, Folder 140)
    - Item 1: The Consumer and Deregulation, 1987; Publication (Box 15, Folder 140)
      Author: Frank Lorenzo
  - Louis Harris and Associates, Perspectives on Productivity; A Global View, Publication (Box 15, Folder 141)
    - Item 1: Loss of Manufacturing Jobs Due to Liquidations, Plant Closings and Other Major Layoffs, 1983; Publication (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - Love, Douglas O., and William D. Torrence, "The Value of Advance Notice of Worker Displacement", Publication (Box 15, Folder 142)
    - Item 1: Labor's Pains, 1991; Publication (Box 15, Folder 142)
      Author: Jeffrey Lott
- Love, Thomas/Sulzmer, George - McKenzie, Richard B.., Publication (Box 16)
  - Love, Thomas/ Sulzmer, George, "Political Implications of Public Employee Bargaining", Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Political Implications of Public Employee Bargaining, 1972; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Author: Thomas Love and George Sulzmer
  - Lovell, Malcolm R., Jr., "Essential Components for Labor Management Cooperation", Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Essential Components for Labor Management Cooperation, 1986; Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Author: Malcolm R. Lovell Jr.
  - Lovell, Malcolm R., Jr., "A Reagan Official Views A Changing Labor- Management Relationship", Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: A Reagan Official Views A Changing Labor-Management Relationship, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Lovell, Malcolm R., Jr., "Employment Security", Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Employment Security, 1988; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Author: Malcolm R. Lovell
  - Loveridge, Ray, "What is Participation? A Review of the Literature and Some Methodological Problems", Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: What is Participation? A Review of the Literature and Some Methodological Problems, 1980; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Author: Ray Loveridge
  - Lowenberg, J. Joseph, "Compulsory Arbitration for Police and Fire Fighters in Pennsylvania in 1968", Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Compulsory Arbitration for Police and Fire Fighters in Pennsylvania in 1968, 1970; Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Author: Joseph J. Lowenberg
  - Lubar, Robert, "Rediscovering the Factory", Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Rediscovering the Factory, 1981; Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Author: Robert Lubar
  - Lucena, Hector, "The State and Industrial Relations in Latin America", Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: The State and Industrial Relations in Latin America, 1988; Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
      Author: Hector Lucena
  - Lozano, Dr. Nestor de Buen; Unna, Lic. Carlos E. Buen A Primer on Mexican Labor Law, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: A Primer on Mexican Labor Law, 1991; Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
      Author: Dr. Nestor de Buen Lozano and Lic. Carlos E. Buen Unna
  - Lumley, Roger, "Control Over the Organisation and Conduct of Work: Evidence From Some Australian Workplaces", Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Control Over the Organisation and Conduct of Work: Evidence from Some Australian Workplaces, 1983; Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
      Author: Roger Lumley
  - Lundgren, Hakan. Companies Within Companies: Introduction to a Series of Case Studies, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Companies Within Companies: Introduction to a Series of Case Studies, 1981; Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
      Author: Hakan Lundgren
  - Lundine, Stan, "The Jamestown Experience: A Case Study in Labor-Management Cooperation", Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: The Jamestown Experience: A Case Study in Labor-Management Cooperation, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
      Author: Stan Lundine
  - Lusk, Kathy. "Creating a Quality Community", Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Creating a Quality Community, 1990; Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Author: Kathy Lusk
  - Lusterman, Seymour, The Organization & Staffing of Corporate Public Affairs, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: The Organization & Staffing of Corporate Public Affairs, 1987; Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
      Author: Seymour Lusterman
  - Lusterman, Seymour, Trends in Corporate Education and Training, Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Trends in Corporate Education and Training, 1985; Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Lynd, Staughton, "Federal Aid For Worker Ownership", Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Federal Aid for Worker Ownership, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
      Author: Staughton Lynd
  - Lyons, Tom Involvement Groups: Toward Joint Problem Solving in the Workplace, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Involvement Groups: Toward Joint Problem Solving in the Workplace, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
      Author: Tom Lyons
  - Lyons, Tom. "The Shared Learning Process", Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: The Shared Learning Process, 1990; Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Mabry, Bevars Dupre, "The Theory of Bargaining", Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: The Theory of Bargaining, 1965; Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
      Author: Bevars Dupre Mabry
  - Maryland Center for Productivity and quality of Working Life, Publication (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Selected Bibliography on Employee Involvement, Union-Management Cooperation and Quality of Worklife, 1987; Publication (Box 16, Folder 20)
      Author: Maryland Center for Productivity and Quality of Working Life
  - Macarov, David, "Job Design and Process Theories", Publication (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Job Design and Process Theories, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 21)
      Author: David Macarov
  - Macarov, David, "Satisfaction and Productivity", Publication (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Ssatisfaction and Productivity, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Macarov, David, "Worker Satisfaction", Publication (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Worker Satisfaction, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Maccoby, Michael, Margaret Molinari Duckle and Robert Duckles, "Bringing out the Best", Publication (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Bringing out the Best, 1980; Publication (Box 16, Folder 24)
      Author: Michael Maccoby, Margaret Molinari Duckles, and Robert Duckles
  - Maccoby, Michael and Douglass Carmichael, "Issues of Participation and Ownership in Productivity and Development", Publication (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Issues of Participation and Ownership in Productivity and Development, 1983; Publication (Box 16, Folder 25)
      Author: Michael Maccoby and Douglas Carmichael
  - Maccoby, Michael, Margaret Molinari Duckles and Robert Duckles, "A Summary of the Final Report of the Project to Improve Work and Management in the Department of Commerce", Publication (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: A Summary of the Final Report of the Project to Improve Work and Management in the Department of Commerce, 1980; Publication (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Maccoby, Michael and Katherine A. Terzi, "What Happened to the Work Ethic", Publication (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: What Happened to the Work Ethic, 1980; Publication (Box 16, Folder 27)
      Author: Michael Maccoby and Katherine A. Terzi
  - Macdonald, Robert M., "Collective Bargaining in the Postwar Period", Publication (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in the Postwar Period, 1967; Publication (Box 16, Folder 28)
      Author: Robert M. Macdonald
  - MacDuffie, John Paul, & Krafcik, John F. "Integrating Technology and Human Resources for High Performance Manufacturing: Evidence from the International Auto Industry", Publication (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Integrating Technology and Human Resources for High Performance Manufacturing: Evidence from the International Auto Industry, 1990; Publication (Box 16, Folder 29)
      Author: John Paul MacDuffie and John F. Krafcik
  - MacDuffie, John Paul, "The Japanese Auto Transplants: Challenges to Conventional Wisdom", Publication (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: The Japanese Auto Transplants: Challenges to Conventional Wisdom, 1988; Publication (Box 16, Folder 30)
      Author: John Paul Macduffie
  - Mackell, Thomas J. Jr., "Review and Outlook- Survival of the Labor Movement: An Unprecedented Challenge", Publication (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: Review and Outlook- Survival of the Labor Movement: An Unprecedented Challenge, 1989; Publication (Box 16, Folder 31)
      Author: Thomas J. Mackell Jr.
  - Mackie, Ann, "Collective Bargaining in the United Kingdom: Recent Trends and Problems", Publication (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in the United Kingdom: Recent Trends and Problems, 1987; Publication (Box 16, Folder 32)
      Author: Ann Mackie
  - Mackin, Christopher, "Employee Buy-Outs as a Response to the Problem of Plant Closings", Publication (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Employee Buy-Outs as a Response to the Problem of Plant Closings, 1987; Publication (Box 16, Folder 33)
      Author: Christopher Mackin
  - Macy, Barry A., Mirvis, Philip H., "A Methodology for Assessment of Quality of Work Life and Organizational Effectiveness in Behavioral- Economic Terms", Publication (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: A Methodology for Assessment of Quality of Work Life and Organizational Effectiveness in Behavioral-Economic Terms, 1976; Publication (Box 16, Folder 34)
      Author: Barry A. Macy, Philip H. Mirvis
  - Macy, Barry A., "A Progress Report on the Bolivar Quality of Work Life Project", Publication (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: A Progress Report on the Bolivar Quality of Work Life Project, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 35)
      Author: Barry A. Macy
  - Macy, Barry A., "A Review and Critique of Sociotechnical Systems Theory and its Accompanying Design Features", Publication (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: A Review and Critique of Sociotechnical Systems Theory and its Accompanying Design Features, 1984; Publication (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Macy, Barry A., "A Systematic Approach to Strategic Work Improvement", Publication (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: A Systematic Approach to Strategic Work Improvement, 1985; Publication (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Macy, Barry A., "A Test of Participation Theory: A Longitudinal Field Study", Publication (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: A Test of Participation Theory: A Longitudinal Field Study, 1984; Publication (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Macy, Barry A., "An Assessment of U.S. Work Improvement Case Studies and Lessons/ Learnings From Other Organizations' Change Efforts", Publication (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: An Assessment of U.S. Work Improvement Case Studies and Lessons/Learnings from Other Organizations' Change Efforts, 1984; Publication (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Macy, Barry A., "The Bolivar Quality of Work Life Program: A Longitudinal Behavioral and Performance Assessment", Publication (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: The Bolivar Quality of Work Life Program: A Longitudinal Behavioral and Performance Assessment, 1979; Publication (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Macy, Barry A., and Ronald J. Grutz, "Organizational Change at Tennessee Valley Authority: The Politics of Institutionalization", Publication (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Organizational Change at Tennessee Valley Authority: The Politics of Institutionalization, 1981; Publication (Box 16, Folder 41)
      Author: Barry A. Macy and Ronald J. Grutz
  - Macy, Barry A., "Socio-Technical Systems Implementation and Employee Involvement: Lessons and a New Direction for the Future", Publication (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Socio-Technical Systems Implementation and Employee Involvement: Lessons and a New Direction for the Future, 1985; Publication (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Macy, Barry A., "The Quality of Worklife Project at Bolivar: An Assessment", Publication (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: The Quality of Worklife Project at Bolivar: An Assessment, 1980; Publication (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Macy, Barry A., and Joseph P. Yaney, "Union-Management Problem Solving for Quality of Working Life: Some Legal Issues", Publication (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Union-Management Problem Solvingfor Quality of Working Life: Some Legal Issues, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 44)
      Author: Barry A. Macy and Joseph P. Yaney
  - Magazine, Alan H., "Human Resources: Restoring America's Competitive Edge", Publication (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: Human Resources: Restoring America's Competitive Edge, 1989; Publication (Box 16, Folder 45)
      Author: Alan H. Magazine
  - Magjuka, Richard "Examining Barriers to Integrating EIP into Daily Operations", Publication (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Examining Barriers to Integrating EIP into Daily Operations, 1991; Publication (Box 16, Folder 46)
      Author: Richard Magjuka
  - "Magma Member Makes History", Publication (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Magma Members Make History, 1991; Publication (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Mahnkopf, Birgit, "The 'Skill-Oriented' Strategies of German Trade Unions: Their Impact on Efficiency and Equality Objectives", Publication (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: The Skill-oriented Strategies of German Trade Unions: Their Impact on Efficiency and Equality Objectives, 1992; Publication (Box 16, Folder 48)
      Author: Birgit Mahnkopf
  - Main, Jeremy "The Battle over Benefits", Publication (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: The Battle over Benefits, 1991; Publication (Box 16, Folder 49)
      Author: Jeremy Main
  - Main, Jeremy, "Detroit's Cars Really Are Getting Better", Publication (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: Detroit's Cars Really Are Getting Better, 1987; Publication (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Main, Jeremy, "Ford's Drive for Quality", Publication (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: Ford's Drive for Quality, 1983; Publication (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Main, Jeremy, "The Trouble with Managing Japanese-Style", Publication (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: The Trouble with Managing Japanese-Style, 1984; Publication (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Main, Jeremy, "Westinghouse's Cultural Revolution", Publication (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: Westinghouse's Cultural Revolution, 1981; Publication (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Main, Jeremy, "Why Government Works Dumb", Publication (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: Why Government works Dumb, 1981; Publication (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Main, Jeremy, "Work Won't be the Same Again", Publication (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: Work Won't be the Same Again, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Mair, Andrew, Florida, Richard, and Kenney, Martin, "The New Geography of Automobile Production: Japanese Transplants in North America", Publication (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: The New Geography of Automobile Production: Japanese Transplants in North Americaa, 1988; Publication (Box 16, Folder 56)
      Author: Andrew Mair, Richard Florida, and Martin Kenney
  - Maister, David H., "The One-Firm Firm: What Makes It Successful", Publication (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Item 1: The One-Firm Firm: What Makes It Successful, 1985; Publication (Box 16, Folder 57)
      Author: David H. Maister
  - Marlin, Martin H., "The Legal Status of Union Security Fee Arbitration After 'Chicago Teachers Union v. Hudson'", Publication (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Item 1: The Legal Status of Union Security Fee Arbitration After Chicago Teachers Union v. Hudson, 1988; Publication (Box 16, Folder 58)
      Author: Martin H. Malin
  - Managing Change Programme, Publication (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: Employment Practices for 1992: Managing the Size & Composition of the Workforce, 1989; Publication (Box 16, Folder 59)
      Author: Managing Change Programme
  - Manley, Tom, The National Employment Act of 2006, Publication (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Item 1: The National Employment Act of 2006, 1990; Publication (Box 16, Folder 60)
      Author: Tom Manley
  - Manley, Thomas, Re-Alignment of Labor Relations in the 1980's, Publication (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Item 1: Re-Alignment of Labor Relations in the 1980s, 1985; Publication (Box 16, Folder 61)
      Author: Thomas Manley
  - Manoogian, J.A., "Quality and Cost Competitiveness", Publication (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Item 1: Quality and Cost Competitiveness, 1984; Publication (Box 16, Folder 62)
      Author: J.A. Manoogian
  - Manpower Inc. "Manpower Inc. Employment Outlook Survey", Publication (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Item 1: Employment Outlook Survey Third Quarter, 1991; Publication (Box 16, Folder 63)
      Author: Manpower Inc.
  - Mansell, Jacquie, "Issues in Achieving Broader Democracy in the Workplace", Publication (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Item 1: Issues in Achieving Broader Democracy in the Workplace, 1985; Publication (Box 16, Folder 64)
      Author: Jacquie Mansell
  - Mansell, Jacquie, Ron Wilkinson and Alan Musgrave, An Inventory of Innovative Work Arrangements in Ontario, Publication (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Item 1: An Inventory of Innovative Work Arrangements in Ontario, 1978; Publication (Box 16, Folder 65)
      Author: Jacquie Mansell, Ron Wilkinson, and Alan Musgrave
  - Mansell, Jacquie and Tom Rankin, Changing Organizations: The Quality of Working Life Process, Publication (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Item 1: Changing Organizations: The Quality of Working Life Process, 1983; Publication (Box 16, Folder 66)
      Author: Jacquie Mansell and Tom Rankin
  - Mansell, Jacquie, Dealing With Some Obstacles to Innovation in the Workplace, Publication (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Item 1: Dealing With Some Obstacles to Innovation in the Workplace, 1980; Publication (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Mansell, Jacquie, Workplace Innovation in Canada, Publication (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Item 1: Workplace Innovation in Canada, 1987; Publication (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Manz, Charles. Keating, David. Donnellon, Ann. Preparing for an Organizational Change to Employee Self-Management: The Managerial Transition", Publication (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Item 1: Preparing for an Organizational change to Employee Self-Management: the Managerial Transition, 1990; Publication (Box 16, Folder 69)
      Author: Charles Manz, David Keating, and Ann Donnellon
  - Marcus, Alan J., James Jandrow and Frank Brechling, "Older Workers and Part-time Work", Publication (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Item 1: Older Workers and Part-Time Work, 1986; Publication (Box 16, Folder 70)
      Author: Alan J. Marcus, James Jondrow, and Frank Brechling
  - Markey, Ray, "New Technology, the Economy and the Unions in Britain", Publication (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Item 1: New Technology, the Economy, and the Unions in Britain, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 71)
      Author: Ray Markey
  - Markham, Steven E., Scott, K. Dow, and Cox, Walter G., Jr. "The Evolutionary Development of a Scanlon Plan", Publication (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Item 1: The Evolutionary Development of a Scanlon Plan, 1992; Publication (Box 16, Folder 72)
      Author: Steven E. Markham, K. Dow Scott, Walter G. Cox Jr.
  - Markham, Steven E., Scott, K. Dow, Little, Beverly L., Berman, Steven "Gainsharing Experiments in Healthcare", Publication (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Item 1: Gainsharing Experiments in Healthcare, 1992; Publication (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Markham, Steven B., Scott, K. Dow. "National Gainsharing Study: The Importance of Industry Differences", Publication (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Item 1: National Gainsharing Study: The Importance of Industry Differences, 1992; Publication (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Marovelli, Robert L. and John M. Karhnak, The Mechanization of Mining", Publication (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Item 1: The Mechanization of Mining, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 75)
      Author: Robert L. Marovelli and John M. Kahrnak
  - Marrett, Pamela C., Cliff Donn and Jack Wilson, "Union Bargaining Power in the Transition Period to a Deregulated Airline Industry", Publication (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Item 1: Union Bargaining Power in the Transition Period to a Deregulated Airline Industry, 1985; Publication (Box 16, Folder 76)
      Author: Pamela C. Marrett, Cliff Donn, and Jack Wilson
  - Marsh, Robert "The Difference Between Participation and the Power in Japanese Factories", Publication (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Item 1: The Difference Between Participation and Power in Japanese Factories, 1992; Publication (Box 16, Folder 77)
      Author: Robert Marsh
  - Marshall, Ian, Industrial Relations and Industrial Democracy in the Printing and Newspaper Publishing Industries, Publication (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Item 1: Industrial Relations and Industrial Democracy in the Printing and Newspaper Publishing Industries, 1986; Publication (Box 16, Folder 78)
      Author: Ian Marshall
  - Marshall, Ray, "Technology Policy in the United States and Other Countries", Publication (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Item 1: Technology Policy in the United States and Other Countries, 1991; Publication (Box 16, Folder 79)
      Author: Ray Marshall
  - Marshall, Ray, "The Transformation of the American Industrial Relations System: Are Unions Obsolete?", Publication (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Item 1: The Transformation of the American Industrial Relations System: Are Unions Obsolete?, 1987; Publication (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Marshall, Steve, "Collective Bargaining in New Zealand: Recent Trends and Problems", Publication (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in New Zealand: Recent Trends and Problems, 1987; Publication (Box 16, Folder 81)
      Author: Steve Marshall
  - Martillano, Gloria T. "Building and Rebuilding a 'Winning Team'", Publication (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Item 1: Building and Rebuilding a Winning Team, 1990; Publication (Box 16, Folder 82)
      Author: Gloria T. Martillano
  - Martin, Ann W. "Work Restructuring in the 1980's: The View from PEWS", Publication (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Item 1: Work Restructuring in the 1980s: The View from PEWS, 1988; Publication (Box 16, Folder 83)
      Author: Ann W. Martin
  - Martin, Gail M., "Industrial Robots Join the Workforce", Publication (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Item 1: Industrial Robots Join the Work Force, 1982; Publication (Box 16, Folder 84)
      Author: Gail M. Martin
  - Martin, James, "A Case Study: The Philadelphia Area Labor-Management Committee", Publication (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - Item 1: A Case Study: The Philadelphia Area Labor-Management Committee, 1987; Publication (Box 16, Folder 85)
      Author: James Martin
  - Martin, Joan, Joslyn Green, and Robert Palaich, Making Teachers Partners in Reform, Publication (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Item 1: Making Teachers Partners in Reform, 1986; Publication (Box 16, Folder 86)
      Author: Joan Martin, Joslyn Green, and Robert Palaich
  - Martin, Julia H. and Achsah H. Carrier, "Training & Education: The Virginia Employer's View", Publication (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Item 1: Training & Education: The Virginia Employer's View, 1991; Publication (Box 16, Folder 87)
      Author: Julia H. Martin and Achsah H. Carrier